<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fine dining on thejerney</title>
    <link>https://jerlim.github.io/tags/fine-dining/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fine dining on thejerney</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jerlim.github.io/tags/fine-dining/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Zafferano @ Ocean Financial Centre Singapore</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/10/zafferano-ocean-financial-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/10/zafferano-ocean-financial-centre/</guid>
      
      <description>Located on the top floor of the Ocean Financial Centre, Zafferano serves up classic Italian dishes using modern techniques and contemporary flavours.
Guests are greeted with breath-taking skyline view overlooking the Singapore CBD and Marina Bay areas, perfect for romantic dates or special occasions.
Dinner started off with Amuse Bouche which consists of a variety of bite-sized canapes from the kitchen.
First up, Scampi e Fegato d&amp;rsquo;oca - charcoal grilled langoustine on top of aged foie gras drizzled with kombu and ginger dashi.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peach Blossoms @ ParkRoyal Collection Marina Bay Singapore</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/09/peach-blossoms-parkroyal-collection-marina-bay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/09/peach-blossoms-parkroyal-collection-marina-bay/</guid>
      
      <description>Helmed by Chef Edward Chong, Peach Blossoms restaurant in ParkRoyal Collection Marina Bay serves up aesthetically stunning fusion Chinese dishes which are as pleasing on the eyes as the palette. We did not have a chance to try them out during our staycation at the hotel earlier this year, and after the most recent P2HA was lifted, we managed to snag the Haute Dining deal to head down for a weekday dinner.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Pavilion @ The Ritz Carlton Millenia Singapore</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/07/summer-pavilion-the-ritz-carlton-millenia-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/07/summer-pavilion-the-ritz-carlton-millenia-singapore/</guid>
      
      <description>Summer Pavilion is a popular 1-Michelin star restaurant located at The Ritz-Carlton, Millenia Singapore which serves contemporary Cantonese cuisine. After reading about Chef Cheung Siu Kong&amp;rsquo;s repertoire of exquisite dishes in various blogs and reviews, we managed to snag the Haute Dining deal to check out for ourselves.
The interior is modern and cosy with elegant furnishings. After being ushered in and seated, the first thing one would notice is the pretty chinaware laid out before you!</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNA @ The Alkaff Mansion</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/una-the-alkaff-mansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/una-the-alkaff-mansion/</guid>
      
      <description>UNA, housed at level 2 of The Alkaff Mansion (an early 20th century bungalow), serves up Basque and Spanish fine-dining cuisine to guests. The Alkaff Mansion is surrounded by lush greenery, while heading up the flight of stairs, I cannot help but feel that I am being transported back in time to a colonial party.
The interior décor with its dark wood theme is warm and intimate, perfect for a romantic date.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skai @ Swissotel The Stamford</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/04/skai-swissotel-the-stamford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/04/skai-swissotel-the-stamford/</guid>
      
      <description>Located on level 70 of Swissotel The Stamford, SKAI (previously Equinox) serves up contemporary European food accompained by breath-taking skyline views of Singapore. When making a booking, I would recommended to specify whether you prefer a table along the windows or in the core area of the restaurant.
Note: While the full height windows provide an unblocked bird&amp;rsquo;s eye view of either MBS or Singapore River, it may be glaring from afternoon sun.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iggy&#39;s @ Hilton Singapore</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/04/iggys-hilton-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/04/iggys-hilton-singapore/</guid>
      
      <description>Well-known by local foodies as one of the best restaurants in the Singapore fine dining scene, Iggy&amp;rsquo;s is located in Hilton Singapore along Orchard Road and is in the 1* Michelin Guide Singapore, since 2017. The food served is primarily focused on seasonal Japanese ingredients they procure.
Dinner started with some bite-sized Snacks. A visual treat on your senses with mini sushi like potato cream balls with green curry and creamy uni (sea urchin)</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
