<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>patisserie on thejerney</title>
    <link>https://jerlim.github.io/tags/patisserie/</link>
    <description>Recent content in patisserie on thejerney</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jerlim.github.io/tags/patisserie/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nesuto Patisserie @ Tras Street</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/09/nesuto-patisserie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/09/nesuto-patisserie/</guid>
      
      <description>Nesuto is a small café in Tanjong Pagar which offers a range of Japanese-French inspired desserts. The interior is simple and cosy, a good place for drinks or cakes if you happen to be nearby having a meal. This is actually my second visit to Nesuto, the first sometime last year after a meal around the area with a couple of friends.
We started off with the Summer Passion which consists of passionfruit mousse, banana compote with coconut creme on a coconut sablee with bits of coconut meringue on top.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tigerlily Patisserie @ Joo Chiat Road </title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/07/tigerlily-patisserie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/07/tigerlily-patisserie/</guid>
      
      <description>The newly opened Tigerlily Patisserie along Joo Chiat Road is the newest kid on the block to join the many new cafes springing up in the East Coast. Helmed by pastry chef Maxine Ngooi whose culinary journey involved stints at Les Amis and the now defunct Michelin-starred Vianney Massot Restaurant.
The botanical themed deco of the cafe has splashes of green and yellow, as well as terrazzo table tops. Do note that seating is limited with the safe distancing measures in place and their cakes are usually sold out in the early afternoon, sometimes even earlier on weekends.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUNA @ Amoy Street</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/06/luna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/06/luna/</guid>
      
      <description>Located near Telok Ayer MRT, LUNA is a local patisserie offering artisanal cakes and baked confectionaries. A friend who worked in Raffles Place area recommended me to visit them as he knows I have a soft spot for desserts. And so, I headed down over a weekend with a couple of friends to check them out.
We started off with the most popular item on their menu, the Orh Nee Cake - vanilla sponge layered with yam ginkgo paste and yam cubes, topped with coconut Chantilly cream, white chocolate pearls and desiccated coconut.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La Vie @ Jalan Besar</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/la-vie-jalan-besar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/la-vie-jalan-besar/</guid>
      
      <description>A couple weeks back, when I chanced upon an Instagram story showcasing an adorable hedgehog shaped dessert at a new patisserie in Jalan Besar, I had to head over and see if it tastes as good as it looks.
La Vie was previously known as Reverie Patisserie, an online patisserie shop specialising in cakes and butter cookies.
The interior of the cafe is simple, consisting primarly of white and greys. The cafe walls are decked with paintings by local artists, doubling as a showroom for interested customer to purchase art pieces which they fancy.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
