<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>staycation on thejerney</title>
    <link>https://jerlim.github.io/tags/staycation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in staycation on thejerney</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jerlim.github.io/tags/staycation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Staycation @ Fairmont Singapore</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/12/fairmont-singapore-staycation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/12/fairmont-singapore-staycation/</guid>
      
      <description>As Sofitel Singapore City Centre was converted to a Stay-Home Notices (SHNs) hotel during the dates we made our Accor Plus booking in Nov, we were offered the option of changing our staycation to Fairmont Singapore, which we opt-ed for.
At the time of our stay, the South Tower of the hotel was exclusively used for SHN. Thus, the Fairmont Gold lounge and newer suites located in the South Tower are unavailable for reservations.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staycation @ The Clan Hotel</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/09/the-clan-hotel-hotel-singapore-staycation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/09/the-clan-hotel-hotel-singapore-staycation/</guid>
      
      <description>The Clan Hotel is a 30 storey modern luxury property by Far East Hospitality, located at unction of Telok Ayer Street and Cross Street (above Telok Ayer MRT). It is a couple of steps away from Far East Square and China Square and across the street is the Telok Ayer bar and cafe area. And if one were to venture slightly further there is Amoy Street Food Centre, Lau Pa Sat, as well we Hong Lim Market &amp;amp; Food Centre.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staycation @ St. Regis Singapore Hotel</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/08/st-regis-hotel-singapore-staycation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/08/st-regis-hotel-singapore-staycation/</guid>
      
      <description>This year, I celebrated my birthday with a staycation at ** The St. Regis Singapore**. Located in the Tanglin district, the property is steps away from Orchard Road, as well as the Botanic Gardens. Do note that there no sheltered access to non-hotel food options (i.e. an umbrella or vehicle is required should it rain)
The check in area is on the left side of the lobby. At each check in desk, there are a couple of seats for guests to sit down while checking in concept similar to The Capitol Kempinski.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staycation @ ParkRoyal Collection Marina Bay</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/06/parkroyal-collection-marina-bay-staycation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/06/parkroyal-collection-marina-bay-staycation/</guid>
      
      <description>Earlier this year, some friends and I organized a staycation cum birthday celebration for a bestie at ParkRoyal Collection Marina Bay (formerly the Marina Mandarin Singapore). After coming out of the level 4 lift towards the reception area, guests are greeted with lush greenery and bird cage like pavilions as they walk across the Atrium Sky Bridge.&amp;lt;
I stayed in a Lifestyle Room (33 to 35 sqm) which came with a city view.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staycation @ The Capitol Kempinski Hotel Singapore</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/06/the-capitol-kempinski-hotel-singapore-staycation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/06/the-capitol-kempinski-hotel-singapore-staycation/</guid>
      
      <description>Located a stone&amp;rsquo;s throw from City Hall MRT, The Capitol Kempinski Hotel Singapore has 155 rooms occupying the Capitol Building and Stamford House. The property is located well within reach of malls like Raffles City, Funan, Suntec City, Marina Square and Bugis, extremely convenient for tourists and staycation guests.
The hotel lobby while small in area, feels classy and the check in process, while seated down on, was fuss-free. What made it feel special was the check-in staff would walk you to your room, feels like you are getting an escort VIP treatment or perhaps it is not too easy to navigate the halls on the upper levels if your room is located in a different wing.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staycation @ The Westin Singapore</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/the-westin-singapore-staycation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/the-westin-singapore-staycation/</guid>
      
      <description>Located within Singapore&amp;rsquo;s vibrant Marina Bay financial district, The Westin Singapore occupies level 32 to 46 of Asia Square Tower 2. The Marriott property is a 5 minutes walk from Downtown MRT station, with Lau Par Sat a 10 minutes walk away to Telok Ayer. During the weekends, its surroundings are relatively quiet, with the lack of bustling office workers, perfect for leisure travellers and staycations.
The building has 2 sets of elevators, one which takes you from the ground level to the hotel lobby on the 32nd floor and the other which links the lobby to the guestrooms.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
