<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>restaurant on thejerney</title>
    <link>https://thejerney.com/tags/restaurant/</link>
    <description>Recent content in restaurant on thejerney</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thejerney.com/tags/restaurant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>L&#39;Entrecote @ Duxton Hill</title>
      <link>https://thejerney.com/posts/2022/08/lentrecote-duxton-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thejerney.com/posts/2022/08/lentrecote-duxton-hill/</guid>
      
      <description>Located on the quaint Duxton Hill area at Tanjong Pagar - L&amp;rsquo;Entrecôte The Steak &amp;amp; Fries Bistro, serves up a Parisian concept of the traditional entrecôte (a premium cut of beef rib) and fries. Do note that there is only 1 main course, which is accompanied by a salad and unlimited crispy fries.
We started off with the Green Salad with Walnuts (part of the main course) and some bread.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Racines @ Sofitel Singapore City Centre</title>
      <link>https://thejerney.com/posts/2022/04/racines-sofitel-singapore-city-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thejerney.com/posts/2022/04/racines-sofitel-singapore-city-centre/</guid>
      
      <description>Located at level five of Accor&amp;rsquo;s Sofitel Singapore City Centre, in Tanjong Pagar - Racines restaurant serves up French and Chinese cuisines.
The perimeter of the restaurant is surrounds by full glass panes which brings in lots of natural lighting and views of the surrounding landscape. The interior is spacious and chic with several sofa seats in the middle.
While waiting for our orders we were served some bread, nothing to shout about in terms of quality but still a nice touch to have.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salted &amp; Hung @ Purvis Street</title>
      <link>https://thejerney.com/posts/2021/11/salted-and-hung-purvis-street/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thejerney.com/posts/2021/11/salted-and-hung-purvis-street/</guid>
      
      <description>Nestled along Purvis Street, Salted &amp;amp; Hung specialises in Australian cuisine with sustainability in mind. The menu revolves around the creative use of forgotten parts, from skin to bones, protein to innards. This cooking philosophy of Minimal Wastage is conveyed in chef Drew Nocente&amp;rsquo;s creations that celebrate diversity of flavours and showcase the beauty of the forgotten.
To start off the night, the amuse-bouche 1 Bite, which consisted deep fried beetroot leaf duest with beet root and yuzu sauce, kangaroo sausage roll, ebi and head cheese.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prego @ Fairmont Singapore</title>
      <link>https://thejerney.com/posts/2021/06/prego-fairmont-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thejerney.com/posts/2021/06/prego-fairmont-singapore/</guid>
      
      <description>Located on the first floor of Fairmont Singapore, Prego is one of my favourite go-to places in town when I have cravings for Italian food. The restaurant décor is rustic Italian and guests enjoy natural lighting from the windows along the sides of it.
Earlier in May, we celebrated a friend&amp;rsquo;s birthday at Prego since he has never been there before and partly because I needed a pizza fix since California Pizza Kitchen closed during the Circuit Breaker last year.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Spot @ Marina One</title>
      <link>https://thejerney.com/posts/2021/05/the-spot-marina-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thejerney.com/posts/2021/05/the-spot-marina-one/</guid>
      
      <description>Headed by Chef Lee Boon Seng, The Spot, serves fusion dishes which mix South East Asian flavours with European style cooking. Located in the CBD, is an ideal spot (pun intended) for holding mid-day lunch meetings or gatherings after work to unwind, chill and drink.
Although not a signature dish, the serving staff recommended us to start with their Cheese Bread - with unsalted butter &amp;amp; paprika sea salt. This savoury morsel, dense in the middle while light and chewy on the outside, is a delight to eat.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
