<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>confectionary on thejerney</title>
    <link>https://jerlim.github.io/tags/confectionary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in confectionary on thejerney</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jerlim.github.io/tags/confectionary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Rose Veranda High Tea @ Shangri-La Hotel Singapore</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/06/the-rose-veranda-high-tea-shangri-la-hotel-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/06/the-rose-veranda-high-tea-shangri-la-hotel-singapore/</guid>
      
      <description>After pampering ourselves the previous weekend with the Language of Flowers afternoon tea, we decided to grab the high tea set from The Rose Veranda at Shangri-La Hotel Singapore last Sunday to end off a busy month of May.
Upon opening the box cover, you would unmistakeably recognize the eclectic pink theme for the high tea set, with the cardboard and various delicate pastries colour synced.
The high tea set includes:</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire &amp; Ice Afternoon Tea @ Capitol Kempinski Hotel Singapore</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/fire-and-ice-afternoon-tea-capitol-kempinski-hotel-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/fire-and-ice-afternoon-tea-capitol-kempinski-hotel-singapore/</guid>
      
      <description>When I heard of a Fire &amp;amp; Ice Afternoon Tea - hot vs cold - it piqued my curiosity as to what type of savoury and sweet delights would be served.
Located away from the bustlings of the main hotel lobby, the Lobby Lounge, decked with dim lighting, comfy chairs and vibrant décor, is an excellent venue for mid-day chilling and indulging in an afternoon tea.
We opted for the five course afternoon tea set which comes with tea pairing for each course.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Langauge of Flowers Afternoon Tea @ Conrad Centennial Singapore</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/language-of-flowers-afternoon-tea-conrad-centennial-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/language-of-flowers-afternoon-tea-conrad-centennial-singapore/</guid>
      
      <description>In early May, Conrad Centennial Singapore launched a new floral themed afternoon tea - Language of Flowers, which includes a range of petite sweet bites and savoury delights. With the recently implemented Covid-19 restrictions, where dinning is prohibited, we decided to indulge ourselves and get a set to share on a lazy weekend.
I have always had high tea dining in the restaurants, this being the first time I am taking away a high tea set.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Champion Bolo Bun @ Tanjong Pagar Road</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/champion-bolo-bun-tanjong-pagar-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/champion-bolo-bun-tanjong-pagar-road/</guid>
      
      <description>It has been 3 years since I last travelled to Hong Kong and I have always been a fan of bolo buns (菠萝包) with Kam Wah Cafe &amp;amp; Bakery listed in my HKG itineraries. Recently, when I heard of Champion Bolo Bun, a new modern concept 茶餐厅 (aka cafe) which opened along Tanjong Pagar, that exclusively sells bolo buns, I had to head down to sink my teeth into them while they are fresh out of the oven.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
