<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on thejerney</title>
    <link>jerlim.github.io/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on thejerney</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="jerlim.github.io/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>jerlim.github.io/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jerlim.github.io/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>Hello! This blog is created primarily to share the food and travel adventures of my journey through life, as well as to pen down my thoughts. Hence, I do not view myself as a food and travel critic/writer.
I grew up playing video/pc games, from Megaman on the NES, Streets of Rage (Bare Knuckle) on SEGA to Command &amp;amp; Conquer RTS on the PC. This love for gaming eventually had a huge influence on me, and I eventually pursued a degree in Computer Engineering (Computer Science) from the National University of Singapore.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>jerlim.github.io/pages/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jerlim.github.io/pages/privacy/</guid>
      
      <description>Who we are Our website address is: https://thejerney.com.
Embedded content from other websites Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
