<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>singapore on thejerney</title>
    <link>jerlim.github.io/tags/singapore/</link>
    <description>Recent content in singapore on thejerney</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="jerlim.github.io/tags/singapore/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Navigating healthcare **** as a caregiver</title>
      <link>jerlim.github.io/posts/2023/04/navigating-singapore-healthcare-as-a-caregiver/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jerlim.github.io/posts/2023/04/navigating-singapore-healthcare-as-a-caregiver/</guid>
      
      <description>The Singapore public health care system is managed by three healthcare clusters: National University Health System (NUHS), National Healthcare Group (NHG) and Singapore Health Services (SingHealth). The patient information records are stored in each cluster’s private system silos, which unfortunately, do not share or communicate with each other.
For several years now, the Ministry of Health (MOH) has been working on a project to connect and exchange the patient data throughout the national health care systems.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNA @ The Alkaff Mansion</title>
      <link>jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/una-the-alkaff-mansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/una-the-alkaff-mansion/</guid>
      
      <description>UNA, housed at level 2 of The Alkaff Mansion (an early 20th century bungalow), serves up Basque and Spanish fine-dining cuisine to guests. The Alkaff Mansion is surrounded by lush greenery, while heading up the flight of stairs, I cannot help but feel that I am being transported back in time to a colonial party.
The interior décor with its dark wood theme is warm and intimate, perfect for a romantic date.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Champion Bolo Bun @ Tanjong Pagar Road</title>
      <link>jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/champion-bolo-bun-tanjong-pagar-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/champion-bolo-bun-tanjong-pagar-road/</guid>
      
      <description>It has been 3 years since I last travelled to Hong Kong and I have always been a fan of bolo buns (菠萝包) with Kam Wah Cafe &amp;amp; Bakery listed in my HKG itineraries. Recently, when I heard of Champion Bolo Bun, a new modern concept 茶餐厅 (aka cafe) which opened along Tanjong Pagar, that exclusively sells bolo buns, I had to head down to sink my teeth into them while they are fresh out of the oven.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staycation @ The Westin Singapore</title>
      <link>jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/the-westin-singapore-staycation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/the-westin-singapore-staycation/</guid>
      
      <description>Located within Singapore&amp;rsquo;s vibrant Marina Bay financial district, The Westin Singapore occupies level 32 to 46 of Asia Square Tower 2. The Marriott property is a 5 minutes walk from Downtown MRT station, with Lau Par Sat a 10 minutes walk away to Telok Ayer. During the weekends, its surroundings are relatively quiet, with the lack of bustling office workers, perfect for leisure travellers and staycations.
The building has 2 sets of elevators, one which takes you from the ground level to the hotel lobby on the 32nd floor and the other which links the lobby to the guestrooms.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Spot @ Marina One</title>
      <link>jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/the-spot-marina-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/the-spot-marina-one/</guid>
      
      <description>Headed by Chef Lee Boon Seng, The Spot, serves fusion dishes which mix South East Asian flavours with European style cooking. Located in the CBD, is an ideal spot (pun intended) for holding mid-day lunch meetings or gatherings after work to unwind, chill and drink.
Although not a signature dish, the serving staff recommended us to start with their Cheese Bread - with unsalted butter &amp;amp; paprika sea salt. This savoury morsel, dense in the middle while light and chewy on the outside, is a delight to eat.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skai @ Swissotel The Stamford</title>
      <link>jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/04/skai-swissotel-the-stamford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/04/skai-swissotel-the-stamford/</guid>
      
      <description>Located on level 70 of Swissotel The Stamford, SKAI (previously Equinox) serves up contemporary European food accompained by breath-taking skyline views of Singapore. When making a booking, I would recommended to specify whether you prefer a table along the windows or in the core area of the restaurant.
Note: While the full height windows provide an unblocked bird&amp;rsquo;s eye view of either MBS or Singapore River, it may be glaring from afternoon sun.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iggy&#39;s @ Hilton Singapore</title>
      <link>jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/04/iggys-hilton-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/04/iggys-hilton-singapore/</guid>
      
      <description>Well-known by local foodies as one of the best restaurants in the Singapore fine dining scene, Iggy&amp;rsquo;s is located in Hilton Singapore along Orchard Road and is in the 1* Michelin Guide Singapore, since 2017. The food served is primarily focused on seasonal Japanese ingredients they procure.
Dinner started with some bite-sized Snacks. A visual treat on your senses with mini sushi like potato cream balls with green curry and creamy uni (sea urchin)</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
