<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>chinese on thejerney</title>
    <link>https://jerlim.github.io/tags/chinese/</link>
    <description>Recent content in chinese on thejerney</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jerlim.github.io/tags/chinese/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>&#43;886 Bistro @ Jalan Besar Singapore</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2022/01/886-bistro-jalan-besar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2022/01/886-bistro-jalan-besar/</guid>
      
      <description>Located along a corner of Jalan Besar, +886 Bistro （八八六） is a Taiwanese café which opened last year, serving popular Taiwanese street food, snacks and beverages like bubble tea. Incidentally, the numbers +866 is the country code for Taiwan if you make international calls.
To start off our meal, we ordered the Crispy Enoki（炸金針菇）. All sides in their menu have an option of topping such as OG Salt &amp;amp; Pepper（椒鹽, Plum （梅子）, &amp;ldquo;+65 Slightly Spicy&amp;rdquo; （微微微辣）, Truffle （松露） or Mala （麻辣）.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peach Blossoms @ ParkRoyal Collection Marina Bay Singapore</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/09/peach-blossoms-parkroyal-collection-marina-bay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/09/peach-blossoms-parkroyal-collection-marina-bay/</guid>
      
      <description>Helmed by Chef Edward Chong, Peach Blossoms restaurant in ParkRoyal Collection Marina Bay serves up aesthetically stunning fusion Chinese dishes which are as pleasing on the eyes as the palette. We did not have a chance to try them out during our staycation at the hotel earlier this year, and after the most recent P2HA was lifted, we managed to snag the Haute Dining deal to head down for a weekday dinner.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Pavilion @ The Ritz Carlton Millenia Singapore</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/07/summer-pavilion-the-ritz-carlton-millenia-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/07/summer-pavilion-the-ritz-carlton-millenia-singapore/</guid>
      
      <description>Summer Pavilion is a popular 1-Michelin star restaurant located at The Ritz-Carlton, Millenia Singapore which serves contemporary Cantonese cuisine. After reading about Chef Cheung Siu Kong&amp;rsquo;s repertoire of exquisite dishes in various blogs and reviews, we managed to snag the Haute Dining deal to check out for ourselves.
The interior is modern and cosy with elegant furnishings. After being ushered in and seated, the first thing one would notice is the pretty chinaware laid out before you!</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
