<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>european on thejerney</title>
    <link>https://jerlim.github.io/tags/european/</link>
    <description>Recent content in european on thejerney</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jerlim.github.io/tags/european/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>L&#39;Entrecote @ Duxton Hill</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2022/08/lentrecote-duxton-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2022/08/lentrecote-duxton-hill/</guid>
      
      <description>Located on the quaint Duxton Hill area at Tanjong Pagar - L&amp;rsquo;Entrecôte The Steak &amp;amp; Fries Bistro, serves up a Parisian concept of the traditional entrecôte (a premium cut of beef rib) and fries. Do note that there is only 1 main course, which is accompanied by a salad and unlimited crispy fries.
We started off with the Green Salad with Walnuts (part of the main course) and some bread.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Racines @ Sofitel Singapore City Centre</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2022/04/racines-sofitel-singapore-city-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2022/04/racines-sofitel-singapore-city-centre/</guid>
      
      <description>Located at level five of Accor&amp;rsquo;s Sofitel Singapore City Centre, in Tanjong Pagar - Racines restaurant serves up French and Chinese cuisines.
The perimeter of the restaurant is surrounds by full glass panes which brings in lots of natural lighting and views of the surrounding landscape. The interior is spacious and chic with several sofa seats in the middle.
While waiting for our orders we were served some bread, nothing to shout about in terms of quality but still a nice touch to have.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Spot @ Marina One</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/the-spot-marina-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/05/the-spot-marina-one/</guid>
      
      <description>Headed by Chef Lee Boon Seng, The Spot, serves fusion dishes which mix South East Asian flavours with European style cooking. Located in the CBD, is an ideal spot (pun intended) for holding mid-day lunch meetings or gatherings after work to unwind, chill and drink.
Although not a signature dish, the serving staff recommended us to start with their Cheese Bread - with unsalted butter &amp;amp; paprika sea salt. This savoury morsel, dense in the middle while light and chewy on the outside, is a delight to eat.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skai @ Swissotel The Stamford</title>
      <link>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/04/skai-swissotel-the-stamford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jerlim.github.io/posts/2021/04/skai-swissotel-the-stamford/</guid>
      
      <description>Located on level 70 of Swissotel The Stamford, SKAI (previously Equinox) serves up contemporary European food accompained by breath-taking skyline views of Singapore. When making a booking, I would recommended to specify whether you prefer a table along the windows or in the core area of the restaurant.
Note: While the full height windows provide an unblocked bird&amp;rsquo;s eye view of either MBS or Singapore River, it may be glaring from afternoon sun.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
